VLADYSLAV POVALII

CONTENT MODERATOR

Warsaw, 02-777 Poland | <u>povalii.vl@gmail.com</u> | +48 513 031 317 https://www.linkedin.com/in/vlad-povalii | https://vlad-povalii.github.io/UdmPractice/portfolio

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Dedicated Content Moderator with a passion for online platform integrity. Also, with 2+ years in Computer Engineering and 3+ years in Sales. Skilled in **user content assessment**, **policy compliance**, and effective **communication**. Fluent in **English**, **Polish**, **Ukrainian** and **Russian** languages, with deep **internet culture understanding**. Proven in **stress management**, **objective decision-making** and navigating complex landscapes. A **reliable team player** delivering results through **attention to detail** and **quick learning**.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Web Developer | Freelance (Warsaw, Poland)

Feb 2023 - present

- Completed over **20**+ projects, improving website performance and SEO for each.
- Creating responsive websites with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

Web Technologies Engineer / Viton (Wroclaw, Poland)

Jun 2022 - Dec 2022

- Utilized HTML & CSS for creating, supporting, and modifying website elements.
- Used JavaScript language extensively for developing and optimizing website functionalities.
- Contributed to responsive website design, ensuring optimal display on all devices.

Sales Representative | Pp Forte-Plyus (Ukraine, Kropyvnytskiy)

Nov 2020 - Oct 2022

- Consistently exceeded quarterly sales targets by over **9%**.
- Implemented new delivery system, cutting processing time by 25% and boosting customer satisfaction.

Document Translation Intern | RPC Radiy (Ukraine, Kropyvnytskiy)

Jun 2020 - Sep 2020

- Translated documents in English, Ukrainian, and Russian for 50+ projects
- Reviewed final works, correcting punctuation, grammar, and translation errors for 100+ documents.
- Participated in 10+ training programs to enhance professional expertise and knowledge

Sales Representative | Pp Forte-Plyus (Ukraine, Kropyvnytskiy)

Dec 2016 - Aug 2018

- Managed and expanded client base, boosting sales by 20%.
- Provided regular activity and results reports to management on a weekly basis

SKILLS

- Keen attention to detail
- Objective Decision-Making
- Emotional resilience
- Strong teamwork and autonomy

- Proficient in MS Office
- HTML, CSS, SASS, JS, BEM, Bootstrap, GULP, NPM, Git, Figma, PS
- Touch-typing proficiency

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering (BE): Web Technologies Engineering

Oct 2019 - Feb 2024

Vistula University - Warsaw, Poland

CERTIFICATIONS

English Language Course - C1.2 (Green Forest - English Language School)

Polish Language Course - B2.1 (Together - Polish Language School)

July 2024

Oct 2023

LANGUAGES

- Ukrainian (Native)
- Russian (Proficiency)
- English (Advanced)
- Polish (Upper Intermediate)

I hereby consent to the processing of my personal data by Accenture sp. z o.o. with its registered seat in Warsaw (00-121), at ul. Sienna 39, NIP 526-00-15-900 (Data Controller), in accordance with the Act of May 10, 2018 on the Protection of Personal Data (Journal of Laws of 2018, item 1000) and the Regulation on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (Data Protection Directive), necessary to carry out the recruitment process by Accenture. At the same time, I declare that I provide my personal data completely voluntary. I also declare that I have been informed about my right to withdraw my consent or object to processing of data, request access to them, rectification, deletion, limitation of processing and their transfer, at any time and the right to lodge a complaint to the data protection supervisory authority.